I also want to join you in this project.
Is your dream exclusive
only for the two of you?
Of course not. You're part of my dreams, too.
Your boyfriend is handsome.
Auntie, this is Hans.
My friend.
You two look good together.
- Liam, your family owns Casa Fuerte, right?
- Yes.
An accident happened
at your construction site.
I should kill people like you.
I am surrounded by useless men!
Spare me, Ramon. I'm a newbie.
This is Lando.
My most trusted gunman.
That face is the last thing you'll see
if you fail again, Danilo.
It's not too late yet.
We can still break free
from Congressman Ramon.
I know I wasn't the best father
for you and your brother.
But someday, you'll understand
that I became a father the way I know how.
I felt like I was dreaming.
I saw Joyce and Sep.
You and Joyce are husband and wife.
You're a family.
My husband became disabled
because of the incident,
but I'm not just after the money.
I want justice.
What will you do with justice
if it brings you trouble?
Maybe I should come back some other day.
Just call me when you're ready to talk.
This place is so beautiful.
But it's so chilly.
I know.
I should have brought my baby with me.
Hey, hey, hey.
We're here for work, not for vacation.
That's not fun. It isn't lovely.
My OOTD is all set.
Director Phil, thank you so much
for staying with us.
At my age, it isn't just about money anymore.
I will do it if the script is good, relevant,
and fights for something.
Thank you so much.
Yes.
This is it, Liam.
We can do this.
Guys!
- Liam.
- Mayor, how are you?
Joyce. Director Phil, everyone,
welcome back to my private resort.
I hope your filming will be smooth sailing.
Mayor, thank you for letting us
film here again.
Of course.
I can't say no to Via.
Wow, I'm amazed by the connections.
But I hope our connections
are clean and honest
so that everybody's happy.
And speaking of Via.
Via!
Mayor.
Good evening. You look lovely.
We're so sorry we're late.
It took a long time
to pull out the other wardrobes.
Why do you look so surprised?
I thought you were just going
to send the clothes.
Are you saying you don't need me here?
No, that's not what I meant.
I can't leave you alone.
You already know, right? I told you.
I'll give my all-out support
for your dream project with Joyce.
Mayor!
Thank you so much for letting us film here.
Via, seriously.
You're always welcome.
My house is your house.
Thank you.
I see you've met my boyfriend, Liam?
He's the creative manager for our movie.
Oh, and of course, Joyce.
Of course!
Who doesn't know Joyce?
But between you and me, I like Savana more.
But then again...
Via's friends are also my friends.
I owe the dela Peñas a lot,
especially Congressman Ramon.
So when I heard Via was part of this project,
I let you use my private resort
as your location.
Thank you so much, Mayor.
But I'm sure everyone's
tired from the trip...
Because I am tired, so...
Of course.
And everybody's feeling cold.
I will bring you to your accommodations.
Director Phil!
Love.
Love...
Did I hear it right?
We got this location
because of your dad's connection to the Mayor?
Honestly, love, I didn't know
that's what his consideration was.
I'm sure he liked your script.
Yeah, but I want to be really independent.
I know you love your dad.
But you saw what he could do, right?
Love...
Don't worry.
As long as I'm with you...
he won't touch you.
I hope so.
I hope he really did let me go.
Because I don't want anyone else
to get involved.
Is there a problem, Miss Via?
Nothing I can't handle, Queenie.
Okay.
The Congressman sent me...
He has Big bro's blessing.
Make sure of that.
We don't want the chief to get in trouble.
Boss, I'm begging you.
You didn't fail me.
This is where our choices brought us.
All we can do now is...
deal with it together.
Do you regret it?
Do you regret being my husband?
If there's something I regret,
it is not being strong enough.
I know I made mistakes
that I cannot rectify anymore.
Sir Liam's script is so good.
It's so heartfelt.
It's so deep.
Well, it shows.
It shows that he is so in love.
That's why he is so inspired to write.
But, thank you.
Thank you for giving this another chance.
We will make everything right.
Love is really something.
Love can move mountains.
But Sir Liam's script... his love...
It feels like it can move
even the longest mountain range.
You're so weird.
I wish he was inspired by Miss Via.
What do you mean, Queenie?
Well, without question, your boss is in love.
But the question is, who is he in love with?
Oh my, oh my.
Our country never progresses
because of issues like that.
You really are an evil queen.
I believe that my Boss Bro
is just following his heart.
If I were Sir Liam,
I would be with the person
who brings me real joy.
I mean, happiness.
Not all love stories have happy endings.
Remember, don't mess with us, evil queens.
Why don't you go in front of the camera?
- It's your fault.
- You were so loud.
Cut!
Good take!
Perfect!
Lovely.
Go call Miss Emmy and Mister Oscar.
This is it, Lord!
Miss Emmy...
Joyce!
Joyce.
Wait.
Why?
Aren't we done yet?
Why? Is what you did not perfect?
Liam...
You don't have to flatter me.
You already have me.
What?
For the film.
I don't want this filming to end.
It feels good to do what you love.
And you're working with the people you like.
This is the first time...
that I've worked without stress.
It feels strange.
You know the feeling of...
wanting to stop time...
even for a short while.
When you don't have problems...
Everything is all right.
If only we could stay brave all the time...
to fight against time.
To go against the flow.
Nothing is impossible if we want it, right?
If only there is magic in our time.
What if there is?
Come on, Liam.
We're too old to believe in magic.
There's no such thing.
But what if there really is magic?
It's beautiful.
Like a film.
These things we see...
That's what real magic is for me.
But what if... there really is magic?
I really hope so.
What do you hope for?
I really hope we can stop time...
at the point in our lives
when we are worry-free.
But let's admit that
even the best film has an ending.
Not all can be done with magic.
Siloy!
What the!
You really are tough.
Edmond, I will repeat.
Where's the money?
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's so loud!
Are you going to tell us the truth?
Or should I bring your young daughter here?
Leave my daughter out of this!
What?
Aren't you going to tell us?
Where is it?
It's gone!
It's me.
Mister Siloy doesn't want to talk yet.
Yes, but I will go there and ask him. Okay?
Okay, thank you.
Bro, make sure they will be there later,
okay?
Sir.
Siloy's wife said
she'd meet you at the morgue.
Morgue?
Siloy is already dead.
What?
These things we see...
That's what real magic is for me.
The film is complete.
Back to reality.
Mom?
What's going on?
Mom, hello?
Mommy, what happened to Dad?
I don't understand
what your father is thinking!
- I thought he had changed!
- Auntie, Auntie.
Calm down. I'm sorry.
What happened?
Dad...
Joyce...
Please forgive me.
I thought you quit already?
I'm sorry, my dear.
It's okay, Dad.
What matters is you're safe. Get well.
You'll recover, okay?
Of course.
Don't cry.
Make sure the public doesn't know.
You know, for Savana.
Noted, Ma'am.
Uncle, get well soon.
Nurse, how's my father?
He's doing okay now, Ma'am.
His lungs got affected by the substance.
That's why he needs oxygen.
But he'll recover faster
if he won't take any drugs.
Josh... We'll shoot the independent scenes
for now.
We don't want to waste time.
We'll shoot while Joyce isn't here...
while she's busy.
Okay?
No problem, Director Phil.
Okay. Please retouch his makeup.
Something bothering you, love?
Nothing.
I'm just wondering if the scenes
we will shoot today are enough.
You don't have to pretend that
you're not worried about Joyce.
Love?
It's normal.
She's your actress.
If you're concerned about the movie,
you're also worried about
what your actors are going through.
Yeah, but... I told her to keep us updated.
Do you want to see her?
I don't think I should.
I'm also busy.
We've got work to do.
We'll take care of everything here.
Right, Borj?
Yes, Boss Bro.
You should go if Miss Joyce's father
is in a serious situation.
We got this.
If I can command the whole fashion week,
I can do this.
It's a small movie in a rustic little town.
Hey.
Go.
Thank you, Love.
Are you just going to let him go, Miss?
Men, like dogs,
should be let out once in a while.
"Who let the dogs out" kind of drama.
I also want to make sure...
if he still knows his way back home.
Okay.
Hey.
How are you?
Sorry, I was busy with work.
The case I'm handling
became a bit complicated.
It was only neglect at first, Joyce,
but the case against Casa Fuerte
has escalated into murder.
Hans, it sounds serious.
I know.
I don't want to jump to conclusions, but...
I can only think of one suspect
who would silence the victim.
Do you think Casa Fuerte
has something to do with it?
It's possible.
So I'll get going, Joyce,
because I still have lots to do.
I will have to check the investigation,
but...
Honestly, Hans...
Honestly, I feel embarrassed.
Your work is important,
but you're here taking care of me.
Joyce, I want to be here for you.
I'm okay.
My dad's okay too.
Okay?
So go do your work, please.
I'm asking you.
I'll be more focused,
knowing you're also focused on your work.
Joyce.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Feel better, okay?
- Yeah.
Liam.
Attorney.
I have to go.
- Call you later?
- Be safe.
Liam.
What are you doing here?
I just want to know how your father is doing.
How is he?
He's okay.
My father's okay.
Did you abandon the filming?
Yeah. I told them I'll be right back.
Excuse me.
This is the call I'm waiting for
from the rehab.
I need to take this.
Hello?
Joyce, your father is... asleep.
Good evening.
- Attorney...
- Madame...
Are you going to move to another house?
Let me know if you need help, okay?
You can call me.
My husband was right.
We should have kept silent.
If I wasn't stubborn,
my husband would still be alive.
There's no justice for poor people like us.
Hans.
Excuse me.
Let's talk later. I'll be right back, okay?
Do you have leads?
I owe you a lot for helping me
solve a lot of cases.
I told you to apply as an NBI agent.
Here. Look at this.
This man was captured by the CCTV
entering this alley
around the time of the murder.
Can I have a copy of this?
Sure.
But it's just going to be
between the two of us.
Closer to each other.
A little bit. There.
We're going to do this in one take, okay?
- Miss Via.
- Quiet, everyone.
- Miss Via...
- Quiet on the set!
Sir Liam's next movie
should be based on your life.
I already have a title for it.
"Love: The Murder of a Martyred Heart".
That's a massacre film.
I'd watch that movie.
My gosh, Miss Via.
Why are we even here?
No hot water, no nightlife, no boys!
It's going to kill me.
Queenie, for an assistant...
you sure do talk a lot, don't you?
I know, right?
But Miss Via,
I'm just verbalizing the feelings
you're bottling up inside.
Do you think I'm happy seeing my boyfriend
fulfill his dreams with someone else?
Especially with another woman?
What happened, Miss Via?
I mean, Sir Liam used to cling to you
like a snake.
But now, you're dealing with
a different kind of snake.
Hey, Miss Via, I hope you didn't
get offended by what I said.
I should go.
No.
You stay here.
We still have work to do.
I'm going to leave.
I'll be working from home.
That's unfair, Miss Via.
Please don't leave me
in the company of mosquitoes and crickets.
I already told you.
Liam is the only reason I'm here.
But he is not here anymore.
You can do it.
Okay?
Miss...
I'll give you a raise
when we get back to Manila.
Okay, back to work!
Looks like you're in a hurry, Via.
Where are you off to?
I'll go ahead, Mayor.
- What?
- But...
- There is something you should know.
- What is it?
My assistant was telling me something.
- She said your town needs more pizza places.
What?
That's not true.
I'll get going.
You know what to do until I get back, okay?
Yes.
Keep an eye on Liam.
I feel so good to be
surrounded by loyal friends.
I know.
Anything for you, Via.
Remember that I'm counting on you
and your family's support
in the next elections.
Come on.
- When did we ever fail you?
- I know.
Wow. The beauty of conditional love.
- That's true.
- It's not too complicated.
- Okay. I'll go ahead.
- Bye.
Hello, Light of Hope?
I had Joyce see a feng shui expert.
I had her wear bracelets and amulets.
She's actually complaining about it.
She said she's not a dog
or an animal to wear a collar.
We even lit candles in church.
You know how showbiz works, right?
Beauty and talent
are not enough to make you famous.
You also need luck.
Looks like I need to
arrange a divination for her.
Why?
Recently, I've noticed...
our amulets no longer work against bad luck.
Ever since... you came.
Let me get this straight with you.
What are your plans for my daughter's career?
To make it clearer...
what's your plan with my daughter?
Joyce and I are just doing
a side project, Auntie.
I'm not stopping her from
taking on other responsibilities.
And based on what I see, she looks happy.
She's happy now because she has money.
But what if it runs out?
Do you think she will still be happy?
Auntie.
I'm sure Joyce knows what she's doing.
And you also know what I'm doing as a mother.
I'm just protecting her.
If she gives up on her ambition,
I don't have anyone else to blame but you.
Everything's set, Mom.
The wellness center
is already waiting for dad.
You take care of your father.
I'm tired
of cleaning up your mess and your father's.
You know the drill.
Make sure no one recognizes you.
Go there later tonight.
[Pares With Love]
Their food is the best.
It really is good, Sir Edmond.
Just call me Uncle Edmond.
And sorry for interrupting your work.
And also you, Liam.
You had to fly here to Paris.
Sorry?
Paris?
Here.
Paris.
It's a store that sells braised beef stew.
When Joyce was still a kid,
she used to cry
whenever I would leave and be gone
for a long time.
So to make her stop crying...
I would tell her about Paris.
I used to tell her I'd go back there
because it was beautiful.
So she grew up dreaming of seeing Paris.
She didn't know
that I was referring to this place.
My Paris.
And that's where I'm going to check-in.
[Light of Hope Rehabilitation Center]
Do you think I'm happy
seeing my boyfriend fulfill his dreams
with someone else?
Especially with another woman?
What happened, Miss Via?
I mean,
Sir Liam used to cling to you like a snake.
Dad.
What are you doing here?
Am I not allowed to visit my only daughter?
My knee is acting up again.
I need you to massage it.
What is this?
Okay.
I'll stay in Paris for now.
Dear, I'm sorry.
Your father is weak.
I wasn't able to fulfill my promise again.
We can get through this, Dad.
I'm not mad at you, okay?
I will never get mad at you.
Bye.
I love you so much, Dad.
I'll wait for you to get out.
I'll be right here.
I love you.
Goodbye.
I can explain that.
Do you still have to do that?
- Ouch!
- Sorry.
Careful!
But...
Liam is just helping Joyce.
Dad, just trust me.
Joyce is his actress.
He's just protecting her.
Only one of us believes that lie.
And that's not me.
You had them followed?
Clearly, you're doubting your boyfriend.
But I don't have concrete evidence.
I still trust Liam, Dad.
He's still mine.
The lies we tell ourselves.
Well, you need to convince yourself.
You even risked your life for him.
You don't know anything.
Liam and I love each other.
Via!
I didn't raise you to become stupid.
I can control the world
in the palm of my hands,
but I have a daughter
who's being manipulated by a man.
I can fix my problems on my own, Dad.
Make sure you can.
Because if not...
I will be the one to solve them, Via.
Before we start...
who would like to recite the Serenity prayer?
Edmond, welcome back.
Go ahead.
Heavenly Father...
Grant unto us the serenity of mind
to accept that which cannot be changed.
Give us the courage to change
the things we can.
Living one day at a time,
enjoying the moment one at a time,
trusting that you will make all things right
if I surrender to your will.
Who will start?
Okay, Edmond.
My name's Edmond.
Edmond Trinidad.
This is my fourth time coming here.
Because no matter how hard I try,
I can't help but escape reality
whenever I remember
the horrible things I experienced in the past.
I've broken my promise to my daughter
a lot of times...
That I'll get my life fixed.
But what you're doing is a good step, Edmond.
You said
you want to escape something from your past.
It's not easy.
But maybe the real solution is
to deal with it.
You only need a strong support system
from your family.
We, here in the wellness center,
can help you
if you want to talk
about what's bothering you.
Free yourself from your horrible past.
Can you do that?
I can.
I don't care if you're innocent.
You're all the same to me.
You will say you took the money,
because you're going to jail anyway.
Where is it?
It's gone!
It's me!
I took the money!
I used it!
It's all gone!
See?
Finally, you admit.
I only want someone who will take the blame
so that the senators who don't like me
will stop bothering me.
That's what you're going to tell the police.
Go get him.
Drag him out of here.
He won't change his statement now.
Uncle Ramon?
Big bro, here's your dessert.
It's not Uncle Ramon's birthday.
What's that?
Where's Uncle Edmond? Can I talk to him?
It will make my investigation easier.
Liam left a lot of debts in Casa Fuerte.
Dad told me about it.
That's why Dad is paying for it now.
Make sure you stay with Via
because if you don't, you'll be dead.
What else do I have to do, Liam?
I know that you know we have a problem, Liam.
Can you tell me the truth?
Are you just staying with me
because you know that if we break up,
my dad might do something to you?
I don't know anymore!
I don't know! I'm getting confused!
I just want to explode!
If he fights me,
he's not the one who will get hurt.
It's the people who matter to him.
I'm sorry
for dragging you into my miserable life.